now let's talk about measuring
performance we have seen that we can
express performance as one over
execution time but the execution time is
on what workload so if we want to
measure performance on two machines and
compare them the question is what do we
run on them to tell which one is faster
than the other and by how much the best
assessment of how do they compare is if
we run actual workloads from a
particular user but this requires us to
run many different programs what we get
is not repres representative of other
users who might be using this machine
completely differently and there is the
question of how do we get the worklow
data even if we found a user whose usage
patterns are representative of many
others how do we persuade that person to
give us exactly what they were doing
with the machine over a course of let's
say a day so when we compare performance
of different machines we usually don't
do this instead we use so-called
benchmark workloads